Universal Negro Improvement Association records, 1921-1989
Emory University
Universal Negro Improvement Association records, 1916, 1921-1989
Universal Negro Improvement Association.
Manuscript Collection No. 1066
11.5 linear ft. (24 boxes) and 8 oversized papers (OP)
Records of the Universal Negro Improvement Association including correspondence, administrative records, photographs, writings, printed material, and material relating to other organizations.
Emory University Manuscript, Archives, and Rare Book Library
Source
Purchase, 2007.
Restrictions on Access
Unrestricted access.
Biographical Note
The Universal Negro Improvement Association and African Communities League (UNIA) was founded in Jamaica on August 1, 1914, by Marcus Garvey. The organization is also known as the UNIA-ACL or simply the UNIA. The motto of the organization is "One God! One Aim! One Destiny!"
After traveling throughout the United States in early 1916, Garvey established the New York Division of the UNIA in 1917. In August of 1918, the UNIA began publishing The Negro World, a weekly newspaper, which reported UNIA activities until it ceased publication in 1933. By 1920, the UNIA had over 1,000 divisions in more than 40 countries. That same year, it held its first international convention in New York, New York, which put forth a program based on "The Declaration of Rights of the Negro Peoples of the World."
After Garvey's conviction and imprisonment on mail fraud charges in 1925 and his deportation to Jamaica in 1927, the organization began to take on a different character and internal rivalries prevailed. As a result, the UNIA continued to be officially recognized as the Universal Negro Improvement Association and African Communities League, but a rival "UNIA-ACL August 1929 of the World" emerged, headed by Marcus Garvey himself after his deportation to Jamaica. From Jamaica, Garvey settled in England where he established and headed the UNIA 1929, until his death in 1940.
Upon Garvey's death, James R. Stewart, a commissioner from Ohio, was named the successor and in 1949 moved the parent body headquarters to Monrovia, Liberia. Unhappy with this development, a rehabilitating committee held a conference in Detroit, Michigan. The committee denounced the leadership of Stewart and the UNIA became fragmented once again. Former High Chancellor Thomas W. Harvey became President General of the new faction and an international UNIA headquarters was established in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania in 1951. At the first International Convention held in August 1953, William LeVan Sherrill was elected President General and served until he resigned due to ill health in December 1958. Harvey stepped in to finish Sherrill's term and was then elected President General in August 1959, a post he held for nearly 20 years, until his death in June 1978.
Scope and Content Note
The collection contains records of the Universal Negro Improvement Association from 1916, 1921-1989. The papers include correspondence, administrative records, photographs, writings, printed material, and material relating to other organizations.
The correspondence series includes letters to and from Presidents General Marcus Garvey, Thomas W. Harvey, and William L. Sherrill. The correspondence documents communications between the Presidents General and other officers and the various Division leaders in the United States, as well as those in other countries. The administrative records relate to the UNIA parent body and its divisions and include minutes of meetings, policies and procedures, and various reports.
The photographs include images relating to the UNIA, in the United States, Africa and the Caribbean Islands. The writings series contains manuscripts and typescripts by several key UNIA officials including Marcus Garvey, Thomas W. Harvey, and William L. Sherrill, as well as others associated with the UNIA. The printed material series includes broadsides advertising various UNIA-sponsored events; brochures relating information about the purpose, programs, and goals of the UNIA; and programs of the UNIA events. The final series consists of records and printed materials created by other organizations from 1921-1989 that were collected by the UNIA. The materials include printed matter such as broadsides, brochures, and programs; minutes, resolutions, and other records.
Arrangement Note
Organized into six series: (1) Correspondence, (2) Administrative records, (3) Photographs, (4) Writings, (5) Printed material, (6) Other organizations.
Separated Material
In Emory's holdings are pamphlets and periodical literature formerly owned by Thomas W. Harvey. These materials may be located in the Emory University online catalog by searching for "Harvey, Thomas W. (Thomas Watson), 1893-1978, former owner."
Related Materials in Other Repositories
Universal Negro Improvement Association records, Western Reserve Historical Society
Related Materials in This Repository
Microfilm copy of the Universal Negro Improvement Association records, 1921-1926, from Western Reserve Historical Society (MCFILM 4025) and the Universal Negro Improvement Association, records of the Central Division, New York, 1918-1959, from the Schomburg Center for Research in Black Culture (MCFILM 3474 REEL 1).
Selected Search Terms
Personal Names
Garvey, Marcus, 1887-1940.; Harvey, Thomas W. (Thomas Watson), 1893-1978; Sherrill, William L. (William Levon)
Topical Terms
African Americans--Colonization--Africa.; African Americans--Societies, etc.; Back to Africa movement--United States.; Black nationalism--United States.; Pan-Africanism--United States.
Geographic Names
United States--Race relations.
Photographs.
Description of Series
- Correspondence, 1916, 1934-1980, Series 1; Boxes 1-13
  Scope and Content Note
  The series contains correspondence of the UNIA from 1934-1980. The correspondence includes letters to and from Marcus Garvey from 1916, 1931-1940. These letters are mostly between Garvey and Thomas W. Harvey and relate to UNIA business. The correspondence also includes letters to and from Amy Jacques Garvey after her husband's death. These letters are also mainly between Amy Garvey and Harvey and relate to UNIA business.
  The majority of the general correspondence is addressed to Thomas W. Harvey (Commissioner of New York and then President General, 1951-1953 and 1960-1978) and William L. Sherrill (President General, 1953-1960). The correspondence documents communications between the President Generals and other officers and the various Division leaders in the United States, as well as those in other countries including Africa, Canada, Caribbean Islands (Cuba and Jamaica), Central America (Costa Rica and Panama), etc.
  Major correspondents include: U.S. Senator Theodore G. Bilbo, A.L. Crawford (Brooklyn, New York), Ethel M. Collins (New York, New York), Solomon Fitghue (Cincinnati), N.H. Grissom (Chicago), Clarence William Harding (Liberia), Samuel Alfred Haynes, Charles Lynell James (Chicago), James R. Stewart, and Naomi Williams Taylor (Philadelphia). The remainder of the correspondence is comprised of letters from individuals inquiring about the UNIA.
  Arrangement Note
  Arranged in chronological order.
  - Marcus Garvey
  - 1916, 1931-1940 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Amy Jacques Garvey [to and from]
  - undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1940-1959 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1960-1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Marcus Garvey, Jr.
  - 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - General correspondence
  - no date (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - no date: drafts (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - circa 1930s (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 1934-1936 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 1937 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 1938 January-April (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 1938 May-December (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 1939 January-April (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 1939 May-December (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 1940 January-April (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1940 May-November (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 1941-1949 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - circa 1950s and fragments (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 1950 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 1951 January-June (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 1951 July-September (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 1951 October-December (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 1952 January-March (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 1952 April-July (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - 1952 August-December (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - 1953 January-July (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 1953 August-December (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 1954 January-June (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 1954 July-December (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 1955 January-August (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 1955 September-October (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 1955 November-December (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - circa 1956 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 1956 January (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 1956 February-March (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 1956 April (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 1956 May (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 1956 June (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 1956 July (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - 1956 August (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - 1956 September (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 1956 October 1-14 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 1956 October 15 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 1956 October 16-31 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 1956 November-December (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - circa 1957 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 1957 January (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - 1957 February (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - 1957 March-April (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 1957 May (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 1957 June (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 1957 July (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - 1957 August (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 1957 September 1-15 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - 1957 September 16-30 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - 1957 October 1-9 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 1957 October 10-18 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 1957 October 19-31 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 1957 November (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - 1957 December 1-15 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - 1957 December 16-31 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - 1958 January 1-15 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - 1958 January 16-31 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 1958 February (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 1958 March (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 1958 April (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 1958 May-July (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 1958 August-December (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 1959 January-February (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 1959 March-April (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 1959 May-July (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - 1959 August-December (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 1960s undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 1960 January-June (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 1960 July-October (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 1960 November-December (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - 1961 January-June (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 1961 July-December (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 1962 January-June (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 1962 July-December (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 1963 January-May (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 1963 June-December (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 1964 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - 1965 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - 1966 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - 1967 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - 1968 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - 1969 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - 1970 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - 1971 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - 1972 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - 1973 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - 1974 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - 1975 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - 1976 January-June (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - 1976 July-December (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - 1977 January-August (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - 1977 September-December (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - 1978 January-March (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - 1978 April-December (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - 1979 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - 1980 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Administrative records, 1926-1987, Series 2; Boxes 14-18
  The series contains administrative records relating to the UNIA parent body and its divisions from 1926-1987. The parent body records include various versions of the constitution and bylaws; policies, procedures, and guidelines relating to the day-to-day operation of the organization; reports, and minutes and agendas of UNIA meetings including the executive council, rehabilitative committees, and the UNIA international conventions.
  Records relating to divisions in the United States as well as in other countries include minutes of meetings, monthly reports of local divisions, charters, and resolutions. Materials may be found from divisions in Brooklyn and New York (New York); Chicago (Illinois); Cincinnati, Cleveland and Dayton (Ohio); Detroit (Michigan); New Orleans (Louisiana); Philadelphia (Pennsylvania); and Raleigh (North Carolina). Records from international divisions include Canada, Costa Rica, Jamaica, Liberia, Nova Scotia, Panama, and South Africa.
  Organized into two subseries: (2.1) Parent body records and (2.2) Division records.
  - Parent body records, 1938-1987, Subseries 2.1; Boxes 14-18
    - General records
    - African Land Project, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Agendas, various meetings (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Aims and Objectives of the UNIA, no date (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Application form for transportation to Liberia, West Africa under the auspices of the UNIA, no date (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Appointments, 1955-1963 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Articles of Incorporation, 1918 [copy] (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Blank forms (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Book list, no date (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Circular letters (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Constitution and bylaws, with amendments, 1938-1955 [pages 1-93, incomplete] (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Constitution and bylaws revision, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Constitution and bylaws revision, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Constitution and bylaws revision, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Credentials (Appointments), 1952-1977) (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Declaration of Rights of the Negro Peoples of the World, drafted and adopted at Convention held in New York, 1920 over which Hon. Marcus Garvey presided as Chairman, and at which he was Elected Provisional President of Africa (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Delegates names and addresses (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Duties of Commissioners (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Duties of International Organizer (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Financial records, 1936-1974 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Five-Year Plan, no date (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Garvey Memorial Liberty Hall (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), records, 1951-1958 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Ghana Project, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - How to Teach the UNIA (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Ideas for Raising Money (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Instructions to Division (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Instructions to International Organizer (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Instructions to the National Youth Director of the Universal Youth Council (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Legal documents, 1951-1975 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Legal documents, Marcus Garvey exoneration, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Liberty Farm, inventory, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Lists, name, etc. (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Mailing lists (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - National Public Relations Committee duties (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Officers: Divisions (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Officers: Parent Body (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Operation Going Home Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Organization chart, no date (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Petition to the President of the United States, circa 1941 [calling for U.S. occupation of West Africa by black troops] (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Petitions to the United Nations, 1945, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Plans for Keeping Divisions Active and Raising Money (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Plans of the Parent Body toward the Carrying out of the Program of the UNIA (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Pledge form to purchase printing press, etc. for Ashanti Akim State College (Gold Coast, West Africa), no date (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Pledges (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Preamble and Manifesto...as announced at their Eighth International Convention...August 1-31, 1946 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Press releases/Announcements (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Proclamations (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Program for African Redemption Fund, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Queen's Contest, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Questionnaire, Conference delegates (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Questionnaire, United Nations (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Rational for Proposed Change in the Structure of the UNIA (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Reorganization UNIA (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Resolutions, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Ritual services, etc. (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Special bulletins, 1953-1966 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Stewart, James R., Prominent people contacted by, no date (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Suggestions as to Procedure in Organizing and Setting Up New Divisions (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Suggestions for Promoting Mass Meetings for Parent Body Officers (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Things to do in Promoting UNIA (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Three Hundred Million Dollars ($300,000,000) Drive, no date (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Universal African Black Cross Nurses, Rules and Bylaws, no date (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Universal Negro Youth Administration, Constitution and Bylaws, no date (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - What We Believe (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Work in Africa Forms, 1961, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Meetings [includes printed programs]
    - Meeting minutes, fragments (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Executive Council/Commissioners (Chicago, Illinois), February 26, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Executive Council (location unknown), June 2, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Executive Council [Emergency Conference], August 19, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Executive Council (Cleveland, Ohio), February 15, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Executive Council (?) (Dayton, Ohio), April 7-9, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Executive Council (Detroit, Michigan), March 24, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Executive Council (location unknown), October 6, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Executive Council (location unknown), April 4-5, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Executive Council (Cincinnati, Ohio), 1954 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Executive Council (unknown location), February 8, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Executive Council/Commissioners (Detroit, Michigan), May 5-6, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Unification Council (Youngstown, Ohio), June 19, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Executive Council (Youngstown, Ohio), October 23, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Executive Council (Shaw University, Raleigh, North Carolina), February 22, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Executive Council (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), August 28, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Executive Council (Chicago, Illinois), September 23-24, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Executive Council (Detroit, Michigan), March 23-24, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - International Convention (Toronto, Canada), August 24-31, 1937 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - International Convention (Cleveland, Ohio), August 15-20, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - International Convention (Cincinnati, Ohio), 1945 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - International Convention (New York, New York), 1946 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - International Convention (location unknown), 1949 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - International Convention (location unknown), 1950 (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - International Convention (Detroit, Michigan), August 26-September 2, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - International Convention (Detroit, Michigan), August 26-30, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - International Convention (New Orleans, Louisiana?), August 20-22, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - International Convention (Liberia, West Africa), September 1-30, 1954 [Stewart presiding] (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - International Convention (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), August 21-28, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - International Convention (Brooklyn, New York), September 15, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - International Convention (Chicago, Illinois), 1959 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - International Convention (Cleveland, Ohio), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - International Convention (Brooklyn, New York), 1961 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - International Convention (Location unknown), 1967 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - International Convention (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), August 30, 1968 [incomplete] (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - International Convention (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), August 28-31, 1969 [19th] (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - International Convention (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), August 27-29, 1971 [21st] (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - International Convention (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), 1973 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - International Convention (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), 1974 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - International Convention (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), August 25-29, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - International Convention (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), August 21-28, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - International Convention (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), August 21-26, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - International Convention (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), August 25-30, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - International Convention (Kingston, Jamaica), August 13-20, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - International Convention, (location unknown), no date (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Rehabilitative Committee (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), August 2, 1943 [agenda only] (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Rehabilitative Committee (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), 1944 [agenda only] (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Rehabilitative Committee (New York, New York), 1945 [agenda only] (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Rehabilitative Committee (Toronto, Canada), August 1946 [agenda only] (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Rehabilitative Committee (New Orleans, Louisiana), August 1948 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Rehabilitative Committee (Detroit, Michigan), August-September 1949 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Rehabilitative Committee (location unknown), March 12, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Other UNIA groups
    - General Conference of Liberia (Monrovia, Liberia), Committee on Medical Services, Annual report, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - General Conference of Liberia, 5th (Monrovia, Liberia), minutes, August 14-15, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - National Emergency Conference (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), minutes, April 1, 1934 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - National Public Relations Committee, program, no date (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Pan-African Community League, program, no date (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - President's Council (Detroit, Michigan), minutes, June 12-13, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Unification Council, minutes, May 22, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Unification Convention (Youngstown, Ohio), minutes, September 10-12, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Reports
    - Committee for the Reorganization of the UNIA, July 25, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Chicago Mass Meeting, June 10, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - High Commissioner to West Africa, 1967-1969, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Trip made by Mr. Solomon Fitghue, International Organizer to Inspect African Project in Liberia, July 22-August 7, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Marcus Garvey Memorial Institute (Monrovia, Liberia), January 7, 1971-December 31-1971 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Ebony Women Conference Retreat, Jun 30-July 1, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Observations on the Status of UNIA of Monrovia, Liberia, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Garvey Memorial Institute (Monrovia, Liberia), March 24, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Committee on Findings for Youth and Education, no date (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Research and Planning Committee Report (Raleigh, North Carolina Division), no date (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Division records, 1926-1977, Subseries 2.2; Boxes 17-18
    - United States
    - Brooklyn, New York (no division listed), minutes, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Brooklyn, New York (Division No. 336), minutes, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Brooklyn, New York (Division No. 404), minutes, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Brooklyn, New York (Division No. 404), monthly report of local divisions, 1956-1961 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Chicago, Illinois (Division No. 401), charter, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Chicago, Illinois (Division No. 401), members, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Chicago, Illinois (Division No. 401), miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Chicago, Illinois (Division No. 401), monthly report of local divisions, 1955-1958 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Chicago, Illinois (Division No. 401), resolutions, no date (Box 17, Folder 9)